Billie Eilish: The World's a Little Blurry is a
documentary, music film directed by R. J. Cutler.
This documentary offers a deeply intimate look at
extraordinary teenager Billie Eilish.
Award-winning filmmaker R.J.
Cutler follows her journey on the road, onstage, and at home with her family as
the writing and recording of her debut album changes her life.
Self, played by Billie Eilish.
Self, played by FINNEAS.
Self, played by Maggie Baird.
Self, played by Patrick O'Connell.
Self, played by Claudia Sulewski.
Self, played by Zoe Donahoe.
Billie Eilish: The World's a Little Blurry is a 2021 American
documentary film written and directed by R.
Cutler and centered around singer-songwriter Billie Eilish.
The film details Eilish's rise to fame since the release of her 2016 single "Ocean Eyes" and the
creative process behind Eilish's debut studio album When We All Fall Asleep, Where Do We Go?
(2019), with the title referencing a lyric from the album track "ilomilo".
The film was released in select theaters via Neon and
on Apple TV+ on February 26, 2021.
The film explores themes of musician, pop star,
coming of age, singer, tourette syndrome.
The tone is thought_provoking.